

George Groff

(425) 418-5397

gegroff@gmail.com

Stanwood, WA 98292

SUMMARY

Accomplished Incident Coordinator with over 14 years of information technology support experience. Tech-savvy professional well-versed in installing and configuring computer systems, diagnosing hardware and software defects and supporting new application rollouts. Committed to providing efficient, high-quality support.

SKILLS

- Service desk support
- Hardware configuration
- Hardware diagnostics
- Technical Troubleshooting
- Software upgrades
- Computer maintenance
- Equipment repair
- Windows XP/Vista
- Hardware upgrades

- MS Office
- Customer service
- LAN/WAN
- Supervision
- Project coordination
- Clerical
- Collaboration
- Reliable and trustworthy
- Planning

EXPERIENCE

1/2009 - 9/2020

Incident Coordinator, Dell EMC, Everett, WA

- Scheduled and assigned work in support of the IT contract with Boeing
- Ensured work is completed per the Service Level Agreement in the contract
- Provided reporting on Root Cause Analysis and tech utilization to management
- Project Coordinator for the migration of 4565 computers at Boeing to Windows 10

4/2006 - 11/2008

IT Deskside Support, AAA Kartak Glass & Closet, Everett, WA

- Provided computer hardware and software support for 50 employees
- Maintained and upgraded over 30 workstations and 4 servers
- Assembled and setup workstations for new employees

11/2002 - 4/2006

Data Entry Clerk, Premera Blue Cross, MountLake Terrace, WA

- Input health insurance claims forms into a computer database
- Ensured HIPPA standards were followed

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

November 2004

BS Information Technology, University of Phoenix

I completed 15 semester hours toward a BS in Information Technology.

April 2006

BA Criminal Justice, Columbia College

I completed 39 semester hours towards a BA in Criminal Justice.

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Dell Global Services Tech of the Quarter, 4th Quarter 2018
- Good Conduct Award, United States Navy 1999